<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Wasiq Bhamla Blog</title>
        <link>https://wasiqbhamla.github.io/website/blog</link>
        <description>Wasiq Bhamla Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to write API Tests using REST-Assured and OkHttp?]]></title>
            <link>https://wasiqbhamla.github.io/website/blog/2020/03/14/restassured-okhttp</link>
            <guid>/2020/03/14/restassured-okhttp</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What is REST-Assured?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>:question: What is REST-Assured?</h2><p>REST Assured is a Java library that provides a domain-specific language (DSL) for writing powerful, maintainable tests for RESTful APIs.</p><h2>:question: What is OkHttp?</h2><p>OkHTTP is an open source project designed to be an efficient HTTP client:</p><ul><li>HTTP/2 support allows all requests to the same host to share a socket.</li><li>Connection pooling reduces request latency (if HTTP/2 isn’t available).</li><li>Transparent GZIP shrinks download sizes.</li><li>Response caching avoids the network completely for repeat requests.</li></ul><h2>:question: How to write API Tests using REST-Assured/ OkHttp?</h2><p>As many of you know that REST-Assured and OkHttp are currently in demand for writing automation tests for APIs. I was learning about Rest-Assured and OkHttp, an idea just popped into my mind, why not save the code on github so it would serve as a learning material for beginners.</p><p>Hence, I created a repository on github(checkout the link below). It has API testing example codes for GET, POST, PUT, PATCH and DELETE requests using REST-Assured as well as OkHttp.</p><p><a href="https://github.com/mfaisalkhatri/OkHttpRestAssuredExamples">OkHttpRestAssuredExamples</a></p><h2>:bulb: REST-Assured or OkHttp?</h2><p>Interesting question! While I was running the tests, I found an interesting thing which caught my attention. The execution speed of OkHttp when compared to Rest-assured was far better.
Checkout the following blog for more details about REST-Assured and OkHttp performance with reference to execution time:</p><p><a href="https://iamfaisalkhatri.wordpress.com/2020/03/10/rest-assured-or-okhttp/">REST-Assured or OkHttp?</a></p><p>In the end, I would like to mention that it all depends on the project and your requirement for choosing the framework to write and execute the tests. Everything has something unique, its up to you how you choose!!</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why is Maven project more preferable than simple Java project?]]></title>
            <link>https://wasiqbhamla.github.io/website/blog/2019/03/03/mavenproject-vs-javaproject</link>
            <guid>/2019/03/03/mavenproject-vs-javaproject</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Introduction</h2><p>Hello Everyone,</p><p>Today we will be discussing about maven and java projects.</p><p>Many people are aware of Maven. But if I ask why would you prefer Maven based Java project over simple Java project?
Many may give just a normal answer like “Maven has the ability to download dependencies automatically based on the dependencies block you put in respective maven project’s pom.xml file”.</p><p>Yes, that’s true and its one of the major bonus point of maven based java project. But there are certain other benefits in maven which when utilised fully can help you a lot in managing and implementing your project.</p><p>Let me describe you all the benefits of using maven on by one.</p><p>So, let’s get started.</p><p><img src="./images/discussion.jpg" alt="maven-vs-java-discussion"/></p><h2>What is Maven?</h2><p>Maven is a powerful project management tool that is based on POM (project object model). It is used for projects build, dependency and documentation.</p><p>How Maven solves the following problems we face in project management:</p><ol><li>It adds all the necessary jars to the project as per the dependencies put ny user in pom.xml file.</li><li>Automatically creates the right project structure.</li><li>It makes a project easy to build.</li><li>It provides project information like log document, cross references sources, mailing list, dependency list, unit test reports, etc.</li><li>Works with CLI(Command line interface).</li></ol><blockquote><p>Following is the project structure of maven project, created in Eclipse IDE:</p></blockquote><p><img src="./images/maven_project_screenshot.png" alt="maven-project-structure"/></p><h2>What is <code>pom.xml</code>?</h2><p>POM is an acronym for Project Object Model. It contains information about project and configuration of the project such as dependencies, build directory, source directory, test source directory, plugins, goal, etc.
Maven reads pom.xml and then executes goal.</p><p>:::note
Following is the sample of pom.xm file:</p><pre><code class="language-xml">&lt;project xmlns=&quot;http://maven.apache.org/POM/4.0.0&quot;
    xmlns:xsi=&quot;http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance&quot;
    xsi:schemaLocation=&quot;http://maven.apache.org/POM/4.0.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/maven-4.0.0.xsd&quot;&gt;
  &lt;groupId&gt;com.mfaisalkhatri&lt;/groupId&gt;
  &lt;artifactId&gt;cucumberpractice&lt;/artifactId&gt;
  &lt;version&gt;0.0.1-SNAPSHOT&lt;/version&gt;
  &lt;packaging&gt;jar&lt;/packaging&gt;

  &lt;dependencies&gt;
    &lt;dependency&gt;
      &lt;groupId&gt;junit&lt;/groupId&gt;
      &lt;artifactId&gt;junit&lt;/artifactId&gt;
      &lt;version&gt;4.12&lt;/version&gt;
      &lt;scope&gt;test&lt;/scope&gt;
    &lt;/dependency&gt;
    &lt;dependency&gt;
        &lt;groupId&gt;org.seleniumhq.selenium&lt;/groupId&gt;
        &lt;artifactId&gt;selenium-java&lt;/artifactId&gt;
        &lt;version&gt;3.14.0&lt;/version&gt;
    &lt;/dependency&gt;
  &lt;/dependencies&gt;
  &lt;build&gt;
    &lt;plugins&gt;
        &lt;plugin&gt;
            &lt;groupId&gt;org.apache.maven.plugins&lt;/groupId&gt;
            &lt;artifactId&gt;maven-compiler-plugin&lt;/artifactId&gt;
            &lt;version&gt;3.7.0&lt;/version&gt;
            &lt;configuration&gt;
                &lt;encoding&gt;UTF-8&lt;/encoding&gt;
                &lt;source&gt;1.8&lt;/source&gt;
                &lt;target&gt;1.8&lt;/target&gt;
                &lt;compilerArgument&gt;-Werror&lt;/compilerArgument&gt;
            &lt;/configuration&gt;
        &lt;/plugin&gt;
    &lt;/plugins&gt;
  &lt;/build&gt;

    &lt;properties&gt;
        &lt;project.build.sourceEncoding&gt;UTF-8&lt;/project.build.sourceEncoding&gt;
    &lt;/properties&gt;
&lt;/project&gt;
</code></pre><p>:::</p><p>Once you put dependencies inside the file and save it, maven searches for dependency in maven central repository and downloads the jar files accordingly for your project.</p><h2>Maven CLI Commands</h2><ul><li><code>mvn validate</code> : Validate the project is correct and all necessary information is available.</li><li><code>mvn compile</code> : Compile the source code of the project.</li><li><code>mvn test</code> : Test the compiled source code using a suitable unit testing framework. These tests should not require the code be packaged or deployed.</li><li><code>mvn package</code> : Take the compiled code and package it in its distributable format, such as a JAR.</li><li><code>mvn integration-test</code> : Process and deploy the package if necessary into an environment where integration tests can be run.</li><li><code>mvn verify</code> : Run any checks to verify the package is valid and meets quality criteria.</li><li><code>mvn install</code> : Install the package into the local repository, for use as a dependency in other projects locally.</li><li><code>mvn deploy</code> : Done in an integration or release environment, copies the final package to the remote repository for sharing with other developers and projects.</li></ul><p>There are two other Maven life cycles of note beyond the default list above. They are as follows:</p><ul><li><code>mvn clean</code> : Cleans up artefacts created by prior builds.</li><li><code>mvn site</code> : Generates site documentation for this project.</li></ul><p>Phases are actually mapped to underlying goals. The specific goals executed per phase is dependent upon the packaging type of the project.</p><p>You can also run the above commands using life cycles commands for e.g.</p><ul><li><code>mvn clean install</code></li><li><code>mvn clean test</code></li><li><code>mvn clean verify</code></li></ul><p>The other major flaw in simple java project is that you cannot run it from CLI also, all the packaging and deploying tasks needs to be taken care manually which is a very tedious task.</p><p>Hope, you have got the basic knowledge of how maven works and why it would be more preferable than the simple java project where you have to do everything manually.</p><p>Keep watching this site for more such interesting blogs.</p><p>Regards,</p><p>Faisal Khatri.</p><h2>References</h2><ul><li>Maven commands have been taken from <a href="https://maven.apache.org">Maven</a>.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction to GitHub Actions Workflows]]></title>
            <link>https://wasiqbhamla.github.io/website/blog/2019/02/23/github-actions-workflows</link>
            <guid>/2019/02/23/github-actions-workflows</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Introduction</h2><p>I have been using different Continuous Integration tools over the period of time for my open source projects on GitHub, like, Travis CI, Circle CI, Microsoft Azure pipelines, etc. But recently, when GitHub announced the beta launch of GitHub Actions, I was excited to try my hands on it. With this post I would like to share my experience using GitHub Actions.</p><h2>Why to use GitHub Actions?</h2><p>When I compared what GitHub Actions has to offer as compared to other CI tools, I was even more tempted to try it out. The advantages which I feel makes GitHub Actions stand out is,</p><table><thead><tr><th>GitHub Actions</th><th>Other CI tools</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>We have more control on the workflow which you create.</td><td>We don&#x27;t have the control when we create the workflow. We are forced to use predefined blocks of config.</td></tr><tr><td>We can create workflow using a simple designer panel.</td><td>There is no designer panel to create workflow.</td></tr><tr><td>The designer generates the workflow config for us.</td><td>We need to manually dig in the docs to find the commands for the workflow we want to create.</td></tr></tbody></table><p>These points were enough for me to motivate to try GitHub Actions.</p><h2>How can you access GitHub Actions?</h2><p>Anyone who wish to use GitHub Actions need to <a href="https://github.com/features/actions">sign up for beta</a> access.</p><p><img src="./images/sing-up-page.jpg" alt="Sign up page"/></p><p>You can sign up for early access from this page.</p><h2>After sign up, now what?</h2><p>After signing up, you need to wait for the mail from GitHub Team who will inform you via E-mail when your access is ready. Normally it will take under a week time but it all depends how many requests they have for accessing this feature. In my case it took more then a couple of weeks when I finally received this e-mail.</p><p><img src="./images/access-granted-mail.jpg" alt="Access grant mail"/></p><h2>You received the access, now where to find GitHub Actions?</h2><p>After the access is granted to you, you can find a <strong>new Actions</strong> tab in any of your GitHub repositories. Let&#x27;s see the tab below.</p><p><img src="./images/action-tab.jpg" alt="New Action Tab"/></p><h2>What&#x27;s in the Action Tab?</h2><p>In Actions Tab, you can create your main workflow for your project. This is what you will see in the new tab.</p><p><img src="./images/inside-action.jpg" alt="Inside Action Tab"/></p><h2>Let&#x27;s create your first GitHub Actions workflow.</h2><p>Now you can start creating your very first workflow from this window by clicking on <code>Create a new workflow</code> button. Once you do that you will see this page.</p><p><img src="./images/first-workflow.jpg" alt="First Workflow"/></p><h3>Step 1. Don&#x27;t rename the file.</h3><p>Use the default workflow file name and path. Do not modify the file name. It should be <code>main.workflow</code>. This file is used by GitHub to execute all the workflows defined in it.</p><h3>Step 2. Edit the workflow name.</h3><p>In the designer, modify the workflow name which you want and select the event when you want this workflow to get executed. For this posts example, I will name it as <code>push-workflow</code> and select <strong>Run on</strong> as <code>push</code> as I want this workflow to run on push event.</p><p>To edit, click on <code>Edit</code> link in the first element in the designer. Same is shown below.</p><p><img src="./images/name-workflow.jpg" alt="Name the Workflow"/></p><h3>Step 3. Add first Action in Workflow.</h3><p>In the designer panel, in the workflow box, there is a blue dot which you can use to drag down to create the first action in the workflow.</p><p>When you drag the blue dot down, a new panel box will get created for your action and a small side panel will also open where you can design the action.</p><p><img src="./images/first-action.jpg" alt="First Action"/></p><p>In this case, I will find <code>Maven</code> action and use it.</p><h3>Step 4. Add command for your Maven action.</h3><p>When you select Maven action, a new panel will open in sidebar. Here you can set the label as <code>build</code>, put the maven command <code>mvn clean install</code> in <code>runs</code> field and put args <code>-DskipTests=true</code> in <code>args</code> field and click on Done.</p><p><img src="./images/cmd-maven-action.jpg" alt="Maven action command to Build"/></p><p>Similarly, you can create many synchronous actions in a single workflow as you want.</p><blockquote><p>I&#x27;ll create one more action to run the tests after build.</p></blockquote><h3>Step 5. Commit the file after workflow is ready.</h3><p>Once, your workflow is ready with required actions, you can commit the file using the commit button on the top.</p><p>After commit, wait for a minute and check in the action tab, your workflow will get executed for any push you do. Same you can see in our example below,</p><p><img src="./images/workflow-in-action.jpg" alt="Workflow result"/></p><h2>Conclusion</h2><p>As you can see with the example in this post, it is like a cake walk when we created our GitHub Action workflow. The possibilities of using actions is limitless as you can use many other ready-to-use actions as per your requirements. Also you can create your own action which can be used by others as well.</p><p>So that was all for Github Actions now, do keep checking this site for more such interesting topics.
If you liked this post then share it in your network using the <strong>SHARE</strong> button below.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beginners guide for Appium Automation for iOS apps]]></title>
            <link>https://wasiqbhamla.github.io/website/blog/2017/04/24/appium-automation-ios</link>
            <guid>/2017/04/24/appium-automation-ios</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Introduction</h2><p>I just completed setting up my Mac for Appium and wanted to share my findings with all. Unlike Windows, the steps to setting up Mac machine for iOS devices is not that easy. We will see the complete steps required in order to get us ready for iOS testing with Appium on Mac OS X.</p><h2>What do we need for iOS Automation?</h2><p>Now we will see what steps we need to follow, so make sure you are following it properly.</p><h3>Step 1: Needs Mac OS X</h3><p>iOS Automation with Appium can only be done on Mac OS X machine so it is advisable to upgrade the OS to the latest version (which in my case is 10.12 Seirra). This can be done from the App Store.</p><h3>Step 2: Create Apple Developer ID</h3><p>Now you need to create your <a href="https://developer.apple.com/">Apple Developer ID</a>. This is required in later steps.</p><h3>Step 3: Install XCode</h3><p>Install the latest version of XCode available in App Store.</p><h3>Step 4: Install Homebrew</h3><p>Homebrew is an easy to use utility to install packages on our Mac. You need to just enter the following command in the terminal, and hit return.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">/usr/bin/ruby -e &quot;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Homebrew/install/master/install)&quot;
</code></pre><h3>Step 5: Install NodeJS</h3><p>Instead of using brew to install NodeJS, it is advisable to use installer package for the latest version available <a href="https://nodejs.org/en/download/">here</a> for installing NodeJS. It is a simple user friendly installer which will guide you in installation process.</p><h3>Step 6: Install Appium Command Line tool</h3><p>To install latest version of Appium, you need to execute the following command in the terminal.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ npm install -g appium
</code></pre><h3>Step 7: Download Appium Desktop</h3><p>Next, download the latest version of Appium Desktop available <a href="https://github.com/appium/appium-desktop/releases">here</a>. We will see in detail how to use this tool later.</p><h3>Step 8: Install ideviceinstaller</h3><p>Install the latest version for <code>ideviceinstaller</code> by executing the following command in the terminal.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ brew install ideviceinstaller
</code></pre><h3>Step 9: Install ios-deploy</h3><p>Install the latest version for <code>ios-deploy</code> by executing the following command in the terminal.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ npm install -g ios-deploy
</code></pre><h3>Step 10: Install carthage</h3><p>Install the latest version for <code>carthage</code> by executing the following command in the terminal.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ brew install carthage
</code></pre><h3>Step 11: Navigate to the bin folder</h3><p>From terminal, run the following command to navigate to the bin folder where Appium is installed.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ which appium
$ cd /to/the/path/returned/above
$ cd ..
</code></pre><h3>Step 12: Install Appium XCUI Driver</h3><p>Install the latest version of appium-xcui-driver by executing the following command in the terminal while being on the path from the previous step.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ npm install -g appium-xcuitest-driver
</code></pre><h3>Step 13: Finding device UDID</h3><p>Connect the device to the machine via USB, then open XCode. Navigate to the menu Window → Devices. Then select your device from left panel.</p><p><img src="./images/xcode-device-manager.png" alt="Device list"/></p><p>Once you select your device, you should see the details as shown, You need to save the device identifier for later use.</p><h3>Step 14: Open WebDriverAgent project in XCode</h3><p>In order to open the project in XCode, execute the following set of commands in the terminal.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ cd lib/node_modules/appium/node_modules/appium-xcuitest-driver/WebDriverAgent
$ open WebDriverAgent.xcodeproj
</code></pre><p><img src="./images/xcode-general-1.png" alt="Xcode General screen"/></p><p>A window like this will open up.</p><h3>Step 15: Enable Automatic Code Signing</h3><p>We need to enable Automatic code signing and deploy the runner project on the device. This can be illustrated as below.</p><p>First, we will select WebDriverAgentLib, and select Automatically manage signing. A pop-up will appear, click on <strong>Enable Automatic</strong>.</p><p><img src="./images/xcode-general-auto-sign.png" alt="XCode General Auto sign screen"/></p><p>Once you enable Auto signing, you will see Team drop down, there you need to select your Apple Developer Account from the list.</p><p><img src="./images/xcode-general-sign-team.png" alt="XCode Auto sign team setting screen"/></p><p>This is shown as illustrated above.</p><p>Now, select WebDriverAgentRunner from the Target list, and enable Automatic signing as done earlier. But this time you will see an Error as shown below.</p><p><img src="./images/xcode-general-sign.png" alt="XCode Auto sign error screen"/></p><p>In order to solve this Error, you need to modify Product Bundle Identifier under Build settings tab from com.facebook.WebDriverAgentRunner to something unique as shown below.</p><p><img src="./images/xcode-build.png" alt="XCode Build screen"/></p><p>Now, again go to General tab to check the Error. Now you will notice that the Error is gone. Same can be seen below.</p><p><img src="./images/xcode-general.png" alt="XCode Auto sign succeeded"/></p><p>Now once, all is set we need to build the project from within XCode by clicking the play button on the top.</p><h3>Step 16: Building WebDriverAgent from Terminal</h3><p>Before building the project, make sure the device is plugged in to the system and you have your device UDID with you, execute the following command in the terminal.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ mkdir -p Resources/WebDriverAgent.bundle
$ ./Scripts/bootstrap.sh -d
</code></pre><p>Once above commands are executed, now execute following build command</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ xcodebuild -project WebDriverAgent.xcodeproj -scheme WebDriverAgentRunner -destination &#x27;id=&lt;Device Id&gt;&#x27; test
</code></pre><p>First time when you build the project, a WebDriverAgentRunner app will be installed on the device, and the build will fail with following Error.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">Testing failed:
 Test target WebDriverAgentRunner encountered an error (Early unexpected exit, operation never finished bootstrapping - no restart will be attempted)
** TEST FAILED **
</code></pre><p>To solve this Error, we need to navigate to Settings ⇒ General ⇒ Device Management ⇒ , and trust the developer as shown below.</p><p><img src="./images/trust-dev.png" alt="iOS Trust developer screen"/></p><p>When you click on Trust button, a pop-up confirmation dialog will appear as shown below.</p><p><img src="./images/trust-page.png" alt="iOS trust developer confirmation dialog"/></p><p>Now, again, if we build the project using the above command, the build will pass and a server will be started. We can confirm it by seeing the build output.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">2017-04-24 16:41:06.470869 XCTRunner[459:77583] Running tests...
2017-04-24 16:41:07.379622 XCTRunner[459:77583] Continuing to run tests in the background with task ID 1
Test Suite &#x27;All tests&#x27; started at 2017-04-24 16:41:08.061
Test Suite &#x27;WebDriverAgentRunner.xctest&#x27; started at 2017-04-24 16:41:08.063
Test Suite &#x27;UITestingUITests&#x27; started at 2017-04-24 16:41:08.064
Test Case &#x27;-[UITestingUITests testRunner]&#x27; started.
 t = 0.00s Start Test at 2017-04-24 16:41:08.067
 t = 0.01s Set Up
2017-04-24 16:41:08.077064 XCTRunner[459:77658] [User Defaults] Failed to write value for key AutomationDisableFauxCollectionCells in CFPrefsPlistSource (Domain: com.apple.Accessibility, User: kCFPreferencesCurrentUser, ByHost: No, Container: (null)): setting preferences outside an application&#x27;s container requires user-preference-write or file-write-data sandbox access, switching to read-only
2017-04-24 16:41:08.079603 XCTRunner[459:77583] Built at Apr 24 2017 15:57:52
2017-04-24 16:41:08.115981 XCTRunner[459:77583] ServerURLHere-&gt;http://192.168.0.104:8100&lt;-ServerURLHere
</code></pre><p>To be 100% sure if all is well with setup until now, open a separate terminal window and execute following set of commands.</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ export DEVICE_URL=&#x27;http://192.168.0.104:8100&#x27;
$ export JSON_HEADER=&#x27;-H &quot;Content-Type: application/json;charset=UTF-8, accept: application/json&quot;&#x27;
$ curl -X GET $JSON_HEADER $DEVICE_URL/status
</code></pre><p>You should see the following output</p><pre><code class="language-terminal">$ curl: (6) Could not resolve host: application curl: (6) Could not resolve host: accept curl: (6) Could not resolve host: application { &quot;value&quot; : { &quot;state&quot; : &quot;success&quot;, &quot;os&quot; : { &quot;name&quot; : &quot;iOS&quot;, &quot;version&quot; : &quot;10.0.2&quot; }, &quot;ios&quot; : { &quot;simulatorVersion&quot; : &quot;10.0.2&quot;, &quot;ip&quot; : &quot;192.168.0.104&quot; }, &quot;build&quot; : { &quot;time&quot; : &quot;Apr 24 2017 15:57:52&quot; } }, &quot;sessionId&quot; : &quot;9F5D94DA-8F60-4A9F-9871-EFCE7F847D8E&quot;, &quot;status&quot; : 0 }
</code></pre><h2>Conclusion</h2><p>Phew!! That was a lot of steps we did in this post. Congratulations on setting up your machine for iPhone Automation with Appium. In the next post, we will see how to identify Elements in the iPhone app and lot more. Until then, happy testing!!!</p><p>If you find this post useful, than share it with your colleagues and friends. If you have any questions or suggestion or feedback, you can share it with me in the comments section.</p><h2>References</h2><p><a href="https://github.com/imurchie/appium-xcuitest-driver/blob/isaac-rs/docs/real-device-config.md#basic-manual-configuration">Appium Docs</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>